I was
walking in the shadows I was living in the grey
Waiting for a signal To help me find my way
I can feel a new connection Like a spark inside
the dark You're my one true direction You're the
fire, you're the spark We're gonna light up the
night Oh, chasing the stars till the morning
light We're gonna make it alright Oh, turning
our color on Shining so bright
We're gonna light up the night
This city sleeps, but we're awake A promise that
we'll never break The future's ours, I see the
sign Just put your hand in mine I can feel a new
connection Like a spark inside the dark You're
my one true direction. You're the fire. You're
the spark. We're gonna light up the night. Oh,
oh. Chasing the stars till the morning light.
We're gonna make it all right. Oh, oh. Turning
our color on. Shining so bright.
We're gonna light up the night
No more shadows, no more gray No more shadows, no
more gray No more shadows, no more gray We're
gonna light up the night, oh, oh Chasing the
stars till the morning light We're gonna make it
alright Turning our color on Shining so bright
We're gonna light up the night
Light up the night
Shining so bright
you